[upbeat music]
- Whoa.
哇。
- Let me see. - No, let me see.
让我看看。不行，让我看看。
- What are you doing? - Ah!
你在干什么？啊！
- Dawn, please, we're in the tub!
Dawn，拜托，我们在浴缸里！
- Yeah, a little privacy.
是啊，有点隐私行不行。
- Oh, I'm sorry, I'll leave you alone
哦，对不起，我不打扰你们了
to spy on the neighbors.
去偷窥邻居。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
- You know, we're not supposed to be spying.
你知道，我们不应该偷窥的。
The FBI was very clear.
FBI说得很清楚。
- They were very clear about the old neighbors.
- 他们对老邻居说得很清楚。
They said nothing about the new neighbors.
他们没提到新邻居。
- Wait, there's new neighbors?
- 等等，有新邻居？
- Yeah, and they have a kid our age.
- 对，他们家有个和我们同龄的孩子。
- There's a kid our age?
- 有个和我们同龄的孩子？
Out of my way.
让开。
Whoa.
哇。
You know what this means?
你知道这意味着什么吗？
all: Oh, yeah.
大家：哦，没错。
- Gentlemen, we have been
先生们，我们一生都在等待这一刻。
waiting for this Moment our entire lives.
这个女孩是我们终于能进入……
This girl is our ticket to finally getting inside...
所有人：树屋的通行证。
all: The tree house.
[轻快的音乐]
[upbeat music]
[听不清]
[inaudible]
哦，你能把那个收起来吗？她会看到你的。
- Oh, would you put that away? She's gonna see you.
好吧，我们只需要过去，
Okay, all we have to do is go over there and
交个新朋友，然后被邀请进那个树屋。
make a new friend and get invited into that tree house.
是啊。
- Yeah. - Totally.
完全正确。
- Tree house.
树屋
- I-- I mean not that the tree house is
我——我的意思是，树屋并不是我们想和她做朋友的唯一原因。
the only reason that we want to be friends with her.
没错。
- No. - Totally.
当然不是。
- Of course not.
哎呀，看起来她已经在交朋友了。
- Uh-oh, looks like she's already making friends.
好吧，他们最好退后。
- Well, they better back off.
那个树屋里可容不下我们所有人。
There's not enough room in that tree house for all of us.
或许可以呢。
- Or maybe there is. - Yeah, I bet it has an open floor plan.
对，我打赌它有个开放式的布局。
- And smart storage solutions!
还有智能储物解决方案！
- Okay! She's free!
好的！她自由了！
Time to turn on that Harper charm.
是时候展现哈珀的魅力了。
Move, move, move.
快点，快点，快点。
Oh, well, hello there.
哦，好吧，你好啊。
- Welcome to Edgewood.
欢迎来到埃奇伍德。
- Hi, I'm Syd.
嗨，我是悉德。
- And we're the Harper quads.
我们是哈珀四胞胎。
- Oh.
哦。
Got to go.
得走了。
- Where's she running to?
她跑哪儿去了？
- Whoa. She got far fast.
哇，她跑得真快。
Ah!
啊！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ One, two ♪ ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Okay, what just happened?
Okay, 发生了什么？
Why did Syd run away? Do we smell?
Syd为什么跑掉了？我们身上有味道吗？
- Pit check.
检查一下腋下。
- We're all fine.
我们都没问题。
But from now on,
但从现在开始，
we check our own pits.
我们要自己检查腋下。
Back to why this girl thinks we're weird.
回到这个女孩为什么认为我们很奇怪的话题。
- Maybe it wasn't us. Maybe it was her.
也许不是我们的问题，也许是她的。
- Yeah, maybe she's just not that nice.
对，也许她本身就不太友善。
- Have you guys met Syd? She's so nice.
你们见过Syd吗？她人超好的。
- Really? - Yeah.
真的吗？
- We sit next to each other in math class.
是啊。
She invited me to come hang in her tree house.
我们数学课坐一起。
She's super friendly.
她还邀请我去她的树屋玩。
- Super friendly?
她超级友好的。
Maybe it is us.
超级友好？也许真的是我们的问题。
- She doesn't even know us.
- 她甚至还不认识我们。
- Yeah, if she's not gonna like us, she should at least know us first.
- 是的，如果她不喜欢我们，至少应该先认识我们。
- I say we go over there, show her who we are,
- 我说我们应该过去，让她知道我们是谁，
and give her a real reason not to like us.
并给她一个真正不喜欢我们的理由。
- Or we could go over there, get her to like us,
- 或者我们可以过去，让她喜欢我们，
and then get in that tree house.
然后进入那个树屋。
- Yeah. - Totally.
- 是的。 - 完全同意。
- I can't wait.
- 我等不及了。
- Not like the tree house is the only reason
- 并不是说树屋是我们想和她交朋友的唯一原因。
that we want to be friends with her.
- 当然不是。
- No. - Totally.
- 不是。- 当然了。
- Of course not.
- 当然不是。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Stop by the tree house sometime.
- 有空来树屋玩。
- Hi, I think we got off on the wrong foot. I'm Dawn.
- 嗨，我觉得我们一开始相处得不太愉快。我是道恩。
- You're on my foot. - Sorry.
- 你踩到我的脚了。- 对不起。
- Hi, I'm Ricky.
- 嗨，我是瑞奇。
- I'm Nicky. - I'm Dicky.
- 我是尼基。- 我是迪基。
You like fro-yo? I know a place.
你喜欢冻酸奶吗？我知道个地方。
- Oh, we live right next door.
- 哦，我们就住在隔壁。
We're super fun, and we really want to hang out with you.
我们超级有趣，真的很想和你一起玩。
- In your tree house. - Or wherever.
- 在你的树屋里。 - 或者任何地方。
- It's not like that's the only reason we want
- 并不是说我们想和你做朋友只是因为这个原因。
to be friends with you.
- 什么？不是的。 - 你真搞笑。
- What? No. - You're hilarious.
- 抱歉，我得走了。
- Sorry, I got to go.
- 呃，不，等等。
- Uh, no, wait.
我们真的，真的，真的很想和你一起玩。
We really, really, really want to hang out with you.
- 你在吓跑她。三个“真的”，真的吗？
- You're scaring her off. Three "really"s, really?
- 我？也许是你的超级，超级，超级小裤子。
- Me? Maybe it was your really, really, really tiny pants.
哦，拜托，我们都知道是Dicky过于积极的冻酸奶邀请。
- Oh, please, we all know it was
哦，拜托，我们都知道是
Dicky's overly aggressive fro-yo invite.
Dicky过于积极的冻酸奶邀请。
- For the record, she hasn't said no.
作为记录，她还没说拒绝。
- What are you talking about? [Dawn yelling indistinctly]
你在说什么？[Dawn大喊，听不清]
- Please stop!
请停止！
I can't be friends with you.
我不能和你们做朋友。
- Sorry. We're not always like this.
对不起。我们不总是这样。
- Well, actually, we kind of are.
嗯，实际上，我们有点是这样。
Once you get to know us, it grows on you.
一旦你了解我们，你会喜欢的。
- No, it's not your personalities.
不，不是你们的个性。
- Oh, good.
哦，那就好。
- It's your reputation.
是你们的名声。
all: What?
什么？
- You're bad kids.
你们是坏孩子。
All the neighbors warned my parents to stay away
所有邻居都警告我父母要远离隔壁的四胞胎。
from the quadruplets who live next door.
嗯，那可能是任何人。
- Well, that could be anybody.
是啊。
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Sorry.
对不起。
- Maybe we should make friends with the quadruplets next door.
也许我们该和隔壁的四胞胎交朋友。
[upbeat music]
- Whoa. There's a lot of activity over there.
- 哇，那边活动真多。
- Bet Syd's having a tree housewarming party without us.
- 我打赌Syd没邀请我们参加树屋的暖房派对。
- How did we get this reputation?
- 我们是怎么得到这种名声的？
We are not bad kids.
我们不是坏孩子。
- Yeah, we're good kids. - Yeah.
- 是的，我们是好孩子。
We're so good, they could make a TV show about us.
- 我们这么好，他们可以为我们拍一部电视节目。
- Totally.
- 完全正确。
"Dawn,
“Dawn，
Nicky, Ricky, Dicky."
Nicky, Ricky, Dicky。”
- No, it'd be called "Ricky,
- 不，那应该叫《瑞奇，
Dawn, Dicky, Nicky."
道恩，迪基，尼基。》
- No, it'd be called "Dicky."
- 不，应该叫《迪基》。
- And?
- 然后呢？
- That's it. Just "Dicky."
- 就这样。就叫《迪基》。
- You guys are all wrong.
- 你们都错了。
It'd be called "Nicky, Ricky, Dicky, and Dawn."
应该叫《尼基，瑞奇，迪基，和道恩》。
- [laughs] That's ridiculous.
- [笑] 太荒谬了。
- Yeah, right. - Who'd watch that?
- 对啊，谁会看那个？
- Seriously.
- 说真的。
- [sighs]
孩子们，FBI说得很清楚。
Kids, the FBI was very clear.
妈妈，我们是坏孩子吗？
- Mom, are we bad kids?
不，当然你们不是坏孩子。
- No. 'Course you're not bad kids.
我的意思是，你们在监视我们的邻居。
I mean, you are spying on our neighbors.
而且那次沙发着火是你们的错，
And it was your fault the couch caught on fire that one time,
但这并不意味着你们是坏孩子。
but no, doesn't mean you're bad.
而且你们在车库里建立了一个秘密俱乐部，
And you set up a secret club in our garage that sent
还让一头斗牛穿过客厅的墙。
a rodeo bull through the living room wall.
而且你们被夏令营赶了出来，
And you were kicked out of summer camp
还被这个州的所有医生办公室赶了出来。
and thrown out of every doctor's office in the state.
而且你被这个州里每一家医生的办公室赶出来过。
And you broke into Candace Parker's tour bus.
你还闯进了坎迪斯·帕克的巡回巴士。
Just rented out our garage to a rock band
只是把我们的车库租给了一个摇滚乐队
and got trapped in a dumpster at the mall.
然后在商场里的垃圾桶里被困住了。
And you have been asked to never return to
而且你被要求永远不要再回到
De Pietro's Wall Oven Pizza, El Pepper Pot, and
德彼得罗的壁炉披萨店，El Pepper Pot，以及
pretty much every other family restaurant in a ten-mile radius.
基本上方圆十英里内的每一家家庭餐厅。
But that doesn't make you bad kids,
但这并不意味着你们是坏孩子，
because that would make your Dad and me bad parents.
因为那样的话，你们的爸爸和我就是坏父母了。
[cell phone ringing] And we are not bad parents.
我们不是坏父母。
[cell phone ringing]
[手机铃声]
Tom, are we bad parents?
汤姆，我们是坏父母吗？
- Did you hear that? We're not bad kids.
- 你听到那个了吗？我们不是坏孩子。
They're bad parents.
他们是坏父母。
- Look, nobody's bad.
- 看，没有人是坏的。
All those bad things have simple explanations.
所有那些坏事都有简单的解释。
We just need to go over there and show her the real "Dawn, Nicky, Ricky, and Dicky."
我们只需要去那边，向她展示真正的“Dawn, Nicky, Ricky, 和 Dicky”。
- You mean the real "Ricky,
- 你的意思是真正的“Ricky,
Dawn, Dicky, and Nicky."
Dawn, Dicky, 和 Nicky”。
[all arguing]
[所有人争论]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
- 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦~
[all shouting]
[众人喊叫]
- Okay, enough!
- 好了，够了！
We figure out the name of the show later.
我们待会儿再想节目的名字。
Right now, we have to keep our eye on the prize.
现在，我们要盯紧目标。
- And there it is.
- 就在那里。
- Whoa.
- 哇。
- Coolest... - Tree house...
- 最酷的... - 树屋...
- Dog poop.
- 狗屎。
What? There's dog poop everywhere.
什么？到处都是狗屎。
- What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么？
- Just for the record, that's dog poop.
顺便说一句，那是狗屎。
- I told you we can't be friends.
我告诉过你我们不能做朋友。
- We know, and we totally respect your wishes.
我们知道，我们完全尊重你的意愿。
We just always welcome new people to the neighborhood.
我们只是总是欢迎新邻居。
- And nothing says welcome to the neighborhood like croquet.
没有什么比槌球更能表示欢迎来到社区了。
It's the game of kings. - And good kids.
这是国王的游戏。- 也是好孩子的游戏。
- Oh, we also brought some tasty food for you to enjoy.
哦，我们还为你准备了一些美味的食物。
- In your tree house. - Or wherever.
在你的树屋里。- 或者任何地方。
- It's not like that's the only reason we want to be friends with you.
- 我们想和你交朋友，不仅仅是因为这个原因。
- No way, we like you for you. - Yeah, you know? - Yes.
- 当然不是，我们喜欢的是你这个人。 - 对啊，你懂的？ - 是的。
- Okay, so why don't we set the spread up
- 好吧，那我们为什么不把食物摆在你树屋里呢？
for you in your tree house?
- 在你树屋里。
I'm sure your party guests would like a snack.
- 我相信你的派对客人会喜欢一些小吃。
- I'm not having a party.
- 我没有在办派对。
- But we heard music and saw a lot of activity up there.
- 但我们听到了音乐，还看到上面有很多活动。
- So you're spying on me?
- 所以你们是在监视我？
- Spying? Us?
- 监视？我们？
That's rich. [laughter]
- 那真是太有趣了。[笑声]
- Spying? More like not spying.
- 监视？更像是没有监视。
- We never spy.
- 我们从不监视。
- You're hilarious.
- 你真幽默。
- Well, if you must know,
- 好吧，如果你非要知道，
I was up there listening to music
我刚才在那儿听音乐
and building birdhouses for homeless birds.
并且为无家可归的鸟儿们搭建鸟屋。
- Aw, good for you. Noble cause.
- 哦，真不错。高尚的事业。
- We do a lot of bird charity work too.
- 我们也做了很多鸟类慈善工作。
- We dream of a day
- 我们梦想有一天
where every bird will have a nest to call their own.
每只鸟都能有一个属于自己的巢。
- But for now, let's dig into this fried chicken.
- 但现在，让我们来享用这炸鸡吧。
- In your tree house. - Or wherever.
- 在你的树屋里。 - 或者随便哪里。
- Look, I'm not buying the good kid routine.
- 听着，我可不吃你那套好孩子的把戏。
Please leave.
请离开。
- Wait, Syd, all those bad things you heard about us,
- 等等，Syd，那些关于我们的坏传闻，
they all have good explanations.
它们都有合理的解释。
- Yeah, we're just victims of circumstance.
- 是啊，我们只是环境的受害者。
- Really, you have to go.
- 真的，你得走了。
- We're sure if you get to know the real us, you'll see.
- 我们确信如果你了解真正的我们，你会明白的。
- Guys, look.
- 伙计们，听着。
It's not that I don't want to hang out with you.
不是我不想和你们一起玩。
It's that I can't.
是我不能。
If I do, I'll be too tempted to do bad stuff.
如果我这么做，我会忍不住去做坏事。
- What? Why?
- 什么？为什么？
- Because the truth is,
- 因为事实是，
I'm a bad kid.
我是个坏孩子。
That's why we had to move here.
这就是我们搬来这里的原因。
And if I mess up one more time, I have to go to boarding school.
如果我再犯一次错，我就得去寄宿学校。
That's why I make birdhouses: so I don't get into trouble.
这就是我做鸟屋的原因：为了不惹麻烦。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
- We won't let you mess up. - 'Cause we're good kids.
- 我们不会让你搞砸的。 - 因为我们都是好孩子。
- Oh, uh, good kids with bacon dumplings.
- 哦，呃，带着培根汤圆的好孩子。
- I do love bacon.
- 我确实喜欢培根。
- Every good kid does.
- 每个好孩子都喜欢的。
- Fine, one dumpling. Then you have to leave.
- 好吧，一个汤圆。然后你就得走了。
Holy mother of pig meat!
天哪，这么多猪肉！
- All right, well, I guess I'll just take the rest
- 好吧，那我就把这些剩下的带回我们的—— - 等等！
of these back to our-- - Wait!
也许你不必现在就走。
Maybe you don't have to leave just yet.
- 培根又赢了。
- Bacon wins again.
- 那我们为什么不爬上你的树屋，在那里你可以享受汤圆和风景呢？
- So why don't we climb up into your tree house,
那么，我们为什么不爬上你的树屋，
where you can enjoy a dumpling and a view?
在那里你可以享受饺子和美景？
- We can't.
我们不能。
My Dad says the tree is old, and he worries
我爸爸说那棵树很老了，他担心
it's not strong enough to hold more than two kids at a time.
它不够坚固，一次不能承受超过两个孩子。
- Hey, no rush, no presh.
嘿，别急，别急。
- Yeah, we'll dumpling down here.
是啊，我们就在这儿吃饺子。
- Tree house later.
树屋待会儿再说。
- Yeah, the boys can set up the picnic table,
是啊，男孩们可以搭好野餐桌，
and you and I can enjoy some croquet.
然后你和我可以玩槌球。
- The game of kings. - And good kids.
- 国王的游戏。 - 还有好孩子。
- Make sure you lock the legs in place.
- 确保你把桌腿固定好。
- "Make sure you lock the legs in place."
I think I know how to set up a table.
我觉得我知道怎么搭桌子。
Why do you have to be so bossy?
你为什么一定要这么霸道？
- I'm not being bossy. I'm being right.
- 我不是霸道。我是在做正确的事。
- Quit arguing. We need to create ambience.
- 别吵了。我们需要营造氛围。
- "We need to create ambience."
- 我们需要营造氛围。
- What are you talking about? - [imitating Ricky]
- 你在说什么？ - [模仿Ricky]
- See? You just whack the ball
- 看？你只需击打球
and hit it through the little loopy thingy.
然后通过那个小环状的东西击球。
- See? The legs are locked.
- 看到了吗？腿是锁住的。
- Ow!
- 哎哟！
[clattering] [cat howls]
[叮当作响] [猫嚎叫]
[tires screech] [horn honks]
[轮胎摩擦声] [喇叭鸣响]
- Who did that?
- 谁干的？
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
I'm keeping the ball.
我要留着这个球。
Oh, I stepped in dog poop!
哦，我踩到狗屎了！
- I can't believe you guys did that.
- 真不敢相信你们会这么做。
- We didn't do it on purpose.
- 我们不是故意的。
- Yeah, that was our Mom.
- 是啊，那是我们的妈妈。
- That was your Mom?
- 那是你妈妈？
You guys are cold.
你们真冷酷。
- We're not cold; we're victims of circumstance.
- 我们不冷酷，我们是情势的受害者。
- If Dicky had locked the legs in like I told him to... - Oh, so now it's my fault.
- 如果迪基像我告诉他的那样锁住腿... - 哦，那现在成了我的错。
- Well actually, it's Dawn's fault; she whacked the ball.
- 实际上，这是道恩的错；她打了球。
- Because Dicky can't set up a table.
- 因为迪基不会搭桌子。
- Told you. - Stop arguing!
- 我告诉过你。 - 别吵了！
You guys are worse than I thought.
你们比我想象的还要糟糕。
And I like it!
我喜欢这样！
Check this out!
看看这个！
[glass shatters]
[玻璃破碎声]
[tires screech] [crash]
[轮胎尖叫声] [碰撞声]
[glass shatters]
[玻璃破碎声]
[tires screech] [crash]
[轮胎尖叫声] [碰撞声]
- I'm keeping this one too!
我也要保留这个！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- I don't see Syd anywhere.
我没看到Syd在哪里。
- Do you think she ditched school?
- 你觉得她逃学了吗？
I mean, now that she's all bad again?
我的意思是，现在她又变坏了？
- Just because she had one little slip-up
- 仅仅因为她有一次小失误
doesn't mean she's all bad again.
并不意味着她又完全变坏了。
Hopefully, she slept it off
希望她睡一觉就好了
and will be back on her best behavior.
并且会恢复她最好的行为。
- Which would be great,
- 那会很好，
because we'd finally get to go up in her tree house.
因为我们终于可以上她的树屋了。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Totally. - I can't wait.
- 完全同意。 - 我等不及了。
- Not like that's the only reason
并不是说我们想和她做朋友的唯一原因。
we want to be friends with her.
我们想和她做朋友。
- Yeah. - Totally.
是啊。
- Of course not.
当然不是。
- Ooh, here she comes.
哦，她来了。
- Good morning, neighbors.
早上好，邻居们。
- Yes, it is a good morning.
是的，确实是个美好的早晨。
A good morning to be good.
一个适合表现好的早晨。
- Speaking of which, we're really sorry about yesterday.
说到这个，我们真的很抱歉昨天的事。
- You guys have nothing to be sorry about.
你们没什么好道歉的。
You were just trying to make me feel welcome.
你们只是想让我感到受欢迎。
And you did.
你们做到了。
I finally feel like my old bad self again.
我终于感觉自己又回到了那个坏坏的自己。
- But what about your new good self?
- 那你的新好自我呢？
- Boring.
- 无聊。
Just like this lame sweater.
就像这件无聊的毛衣一样。
- What's wrong with that sweater?
- 这件毛衣有什么问题？
It's just like mine.
它和我的那件很像。
- It's fine for you, but I look better in this.
- 对你来说没问题，但我穿这件更好看。
- Whoa.
- 哇。
You do look pretty awesome.
你看起来确实很棒。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
Now, let's go break something.
现在，我们去搞点破坏吧。
- Wait, aren't you afraid of getting caught?
等等，你不怕被抓吗？
Remember? Boarding school?
记得吗？我们上的是寄宿学校。
- I'm not gonna get caught.
我不会被抓的。
So you with me?
那你跟我一起吗？
We can do a lot of damage before homeroom.
我们可以在早自习前搞很多破坏。
- Uh, no, thanks. I'm kind of a "by the rules" kind of guy.
呃，不了，谢谢。我是个遵守规则的人。
- Me too, but thanks for asking.
我也是，不过谢谢你邀请我。
- I've got a spotless record, so no can do.
- 我的记录无可挑剔，所以不行。
- I would, but these three get kind of judge-y.
- 我本来愿意的，但这三位有点评头论足。
- I knew you guys weren't really bad.
- 我就知道你们不是真的坏。
- Hold on; we're too bad
- 等等；我们太坏了
to hang out with you when you're good,
不能在你好的时候和你玩，
but when you're bad, we're not bad enough?
但当你坏的时候，我们又不够坏？
- Pretty much. See ya.
- 差不多。再见。
- This is terrible.
- 这太糟糕了。
- She's gonna get caught. - And sent away.
- 她会被抓到的。 - 还会被送走。
- And it's our fault she turned bad again.
- 而且是我们让她再次变坏的。
So we need to do the right thing:
所以我们需要做正确的事：
follow her around and stop her from doing the wrong thing.
跟着她，阻止她做错事。
- So we can get into that tree house.
这样我们就能进入那个树屋。
- Yeah. - Totally.
对。
- I can't wait.
完全同意。
- Not like that is the only reason that we want to be friends with her.
我等不及了。
- Yeah. - No.
并不是说我们想和她做朋友只是因为这个原因。
- Of course not.
对。
- [gasps] Uh-oh.
不是的。
Syd's on the library table.
当然不是。
- What is she doing?
- 她在做什么？
- I'm not sure if it's a whip or a nae nae, but I'm certain it's a no-no.
- 我不确定那是鞭打还是Nae Nae舞，但我确信那是不允许的。
[upbeat music]
- I lost Syd in the cafeteria. Have you guys seen her?
- 我在食堂把Syd弄丢了。你们看到她了吗？
- No, but I think she drew a moustache on the lunch lady.
- 没有，但我觉得她在午餐阿姨脸上画了小胡子。
- That was already there.
- 那本来就在那儿。
- Well, that's good news for us but bad news for Mr. Lunch Lady.
- 嗯，这对我们来说是好消息，但对午餐阿姨先生来说却是坏消息。
- I don't see how we can keep this up.
- 我不知道我们怎么能继续这样下去。
I've already been tardy to two classes.
我已经迟到两节课了。
I don't do tardy.
我不迟到。
- Hey, guys. - Have you seen Syd?
嘿，伙计们。
- Not since Mr. Williams' class.
你们见过Syd吗？
Have you guys noticed that she seems different today?
自从Williams老师的课后就没见了。
- No. - Didn't notice.
你们发现她今天好像有点不一样吗？
- The same old Syd.
没注意到。
- We didn't do a thing to change her.
还是老样子的Syd。
- Dicky.
我们可没做任何事去改变她。
- Speaking of Mr. Williams,
Dicky。
did you hear someone stole his answer book?
说起Williams老师，
- Guys, this is not good.
听说有人偷了他的答案本？
- No, it is good. He cancelled tomorrow's test.
不，这是好事。他取消了明天的考试。
Now I have time to paint my kitty's claws
现在我有时间给我的小猫涂指甲了
before her birthday party.
在她生日派对之前。
It's her cats-eañera.
这是她的猫咪派对。
- Okay, I know Syd is a bad kid,
好吧，我知道Syd是个坏孩子，
but I don't think she'd do something this bad.
但我不认为她会做这么糟糕的事。
- Yeah, there's no way she stole the answer book.
是的，她不可能偷了答案书。
She stole the answer book.
她偷了答案书。
- And now she's climbing back down without it.
而现在她正爬下来，没有带着它。
She hid it in the tree house.
她把它藏在树屋里了。
If she gets caught with that book,
如果她被发现带着那本书，
it's "hello, boarding school" for her
她就要去寄宿学校了，
and "good-bye, tree house" for us.
而我们就要失去树屋了。
- But again, it's not like that's the only reason
- 但话说回来，这并不是我们想和她做朋友的唯一原因。
we want to be friends with her.
- 是啊。 - 不是。
- Yeah. - No.
- 当然不是。
- Of course not.
- 你非得现在洗澡吗？
- Did you have to take a bath now?
- 我先来的。
- I was here first.
- 好吧，我要跑去Syd那里把书拿回来，
- Okay, I'm gonna run over to Syd's and get that book back
这样Mr. Williams就不会发现了。
so Mr. Williams doesn't find out.
这样威廉姆斯先生就不会发现了。
- Why do you get to be the one who goes in the tree house?
你为什么能去树屋？
- Because I'm the only one wearing socks and shoes.
因为我穿了袜子和鞋子。
- Good. She's gone.
好。她走了。
Don't need these anymore.
这些不再需要了。
both: No!
不！
[upbeat music]
- Whoa.
哇。
Look at this place.
看看这个地方。
Snacks, TV,
零食，电视，
feather boas.
羽毛围巾。
- Did she find the book yet? - Doesn't look like it.
- 她找到那本书了吗？ - 看起来没有。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Okay, focus, Dawn. Have to find that answer key.
- 好吧，专注，Dawn。必须找到那个答案键。
Where could it...
它可能在哪儿...
- Oh, no. Here comes Syd.
- 哦，不。Syd来了。
And she's got a crowbar.
而且她拿着撬棍。
- Oh, we've got to call Dawn and warn her.
- 哦，我们得打电话给Dawn警告她。
[cell phone ringing]
[手机铃声]
- Hello, Dawn Harper's phone.
- 你好，Dawn Harper的手机。
- Really?
真的吗？
- I don't know who it was, but they just hung up on me.
我不知道是谁，但他们刚刚挂断了我的电话。
- Oh.
哦。
- Dawn found the book.
Dawn找到了那本书。
- Okay.
好的。
- [gasps]
（喘气声）
Dawn?
Dawn？
What are you doing up here?
你在这里做什么？
- Uh, I was looking for this.
呃，我在找这个。
We saw you hide it up here.
我们看到你把它藏在这里了。
[inaudible]
[听不清]
- Oh, Syd does not look happy.
哦，Syd看起来不高兴。
- You were spying on me? Again?
你们在监视我？又来了？
The FBI should really look into you guys.
FBI真该调查你们这些人。
- Oh, they have.
哦，他们已经调查过了。
We were only spying on you to look out for you.
我们只是监视你，为了保护你。
I thought if I could sneak this answer book back
我想如果我能偷偷把这本答案书放回
into Mr. Williams' desk, it would save you.
Williams先生的桌子里，就能救你。
- I don't want to be saved.
我不想被救。
Except from that bee.
除了那只蜜蜂。
I really hate bees.
我真的讨厌蜜蜂。
- Look, there's nothing to worry about.
瞧，没什么好担心的。
Ah! Bee!
啊！蜜蜂！
- Dawn's fighting her way out.
Dawn正在奋力脱身。
- Okay.
好吧。
I think I scared it away.
我想我把它吓跑了。
But, look, we're only trying to help you.
但是，我们只是想帮你。
- If you really want to help, hand me that can of paint.
如果你真的想帮忙，把那罐油漆递给我。
- Oh, were you going to paint the birdhouses red?
哦，你打算把鸟屋漆成红色吗？
See, now, that's good.
看，现在，这很好。
- Forget birdhouses; I'm gonna take these balloons
- 别管鸟屋了；我要用这些气球
and fill them with red paint and throw them at cars.
装满红漆，然后扔向汽车。
- See, now, that's bad.
- 看，这样不好。
- Relax. It's gonna be fun.
- 放松。会很有趣的。
Here, let me open that can. I'll show you.
来，让我打开那罐。我示范给你看。
- No.
- 不行。
- Syd's going after her with the crowbar.
- Syd拿着撬棍追她去了。
- I'm not gonna let you do this.
- 我不会让你这么做的。
[grunts] [paint can clanking]
[咕哝声] [油漆罐碰撞声]
- Ah! - What is it?
- 啊！ - 怎么了？
Ah! - What is it?
啊！- 怎么了？
Ah! - We got to get over there.
啊！- 我们得赶紧过去。
Now!
现在！
- In case they call back.
- 以防他们再打来。
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- Stop hurting our sister!
- 别再伤害我们的妹妹了！
- Guys.
- 大家。
- Yeah, you mess with her, you mess with all of us.
- 是的，你惹她就是惹我们所有人。
- Guys.
- 大家。
- I am not one for roughhousing,
我不喜欢打闹，
but I will throw down for my sister.
但为了我妹妹，我愿意出手。
- Guys.
大家。
I'm okay.
我没事。
- But then what's with all the blood?
那这些血是怎么回事？
- Uh, it's not blood.
呃，这不是血。
It's red paint.
是红漆。
- Oh, thank goodness.
哦，谢天谢地。
I really don't know how to throw down.
我真的不知道怎么打架。
- I would never hurt Dawn.
我绝不会伤害Dawn。
- Well, ever since we turned you bad again,
- 自从我们再次把你变成坏人后，
we didn't know what you were capable of.
我们不知道你能做出什么来。
- Do you really want to go to boarding school?
- 你真的想去寄宿学校吗？
- No.
- 不。
The four of you are lucky.
你们四个真幸运。
You look out for each other.
你们互相照顾。
I guess I'm lucky you've been looking out for me.
我想我也幸运有你们照顾我。
- Hey, that's what friends do for each other.
- 嘿，这就是朋友之间该做的。
- Guys, look at this place. - Yeah, it's amazing.
- 伙计们，看看这个地方。 - 是啊，太惊人了。
- Look at all the smart storage solutions.
- 看看所有的智能存储解决方案。
- Hey, there's five of us up here.
嘿，这里有我们五个人。
- Huh. My Dad was wrong.
嗯，我爸爸错了。
This thing can hold more than two people.
这东西能容纳不止两个人。
Guess the tree's stronger than he thought.
看来这棵树比他想的要结实。
all: Aww.
哎呀。
[creaking]
[吱嘎声]
- What was that?
那是什么声音？
[rumbling]
[隆隆声]
- Wow.
哇。
Fell to the ground, and it's--
掉到地上了，而且——
it's still in one piece.
它还是完好无损的。
- I guess it's not a total disaster.
我想这还不算彻底的灾难。
- Yeah.
是啊。
- What?
什么？
- Now it's a total disaster.
现在变成彻底的灾难了。
- I guess we all shouldn't have gone up there at the same time.
我想我们都不该同时上去的。
- Once again, victims of circumstance.
又一次，成了环境的牺牲品。
We tried to do something good, and something bad happened.
我们尝试做点好事，却发生了坏事。
[bang]
砰！
It never ends.
这永远不会结束。
- It's okay.
- 没关系。
You may have ruined my tree house,
你也许毁了我的树屋，
but you've given me something much more valuable:
但你给了我更宝贵的东西：
your friendship. - Aw.
你的友谊。 - 噢。
- And I know something we friends can do together
- 而且我知道我们朋友可以一起做
that's better than hanging in a silly old tree house.
比在那个傻乎乎的旧树屋里晃荡更好的事情。
You know, I used to find this boring,
你知道吗，我以前觉得这很无聊，
but now that I'm doing it with friends, it's kind of fun.
但现在和朋友一起做，感觉挺有趣的。
- Yeah. This is great.
- 是啊。这真棒。
- So much fun.
- 太有趣了。
- Way better than hanging out in a tree house.
比在树屋里闲逛好多了。
- I have a splinter.
我扎了个刺。
- You know, I used to think
你知道吗，我以前以为
you guys were just using me for my tree house,
你们只是利用我的树屋，
but now I can see that our friendship is built to last.
但现在我看得出我们的友谊是长久的。
- Oh, well. - I guess that's it for today.
哦，好吧。
- Got to go.
我想今天就到这里吧。
♪ ♪
得走了。
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 是啊！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 是啊！ ♪